<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes" ?>
<file name="TXT\en\MISS_005.ENG" compressed="true">
<text extractedid="0">
We are surrounded by nothing but barren wilderness. The edges of this world seem to be either impenetrable mountains or lava flows.

It is impossible to keep track of time here. A dim, perpetual twilight hangs over everything and there is neither sunlight nor starlight.

What wonders and dangers lie hidden here?















</text>
<text extractedid="1">
Keep looking for the gateway. There is limited space for buildings; carefully consider how to exploit your resources.
</text>
<text extractedid="2">
We have met humans of much stranger appearance than our Viking shipwright. 
They call themselves "Sons of Nippon." They are short and thin but obviously skilled and tenacious. Their strangest feature is their skin color. It is yellow ochre and their eyes are just small slits. They act in a friendly manner although they are unsettling to behold because of their strange appearance.
</text>
<text extractedid="3">

</text>
<text extractedid="4">
The "Sons of Nippon" in the south have relatives in the north. Their relationship with each other appears very friendly. War with one race means war with the other. We must consider the prospect of war carefully...
</text>
<text extractedid="5">

</text>
<text extractedid="6">
We have found the gateway and occupied it. We can go through it whenever we want!


















</text>
<text extractedid="7">
You have completed this mission. The next Chapter awaits you...
</text>
<notext extractedid="8" />
<notext extractedid="9" />
<notext extractedid="10" />
<notext extractedid="11" />
<notext extractedid="12" />
<notext extractedid="13" />
<notext extractedid="14" />
<notext extractedid="15" />
<notext extractedid="16" />
<notext extractedid="17" />
<notext extractedid="18" />
<notext extractedid="19" />
<notext extractedid="20" />
<notext extractedid="21" />
<notext extractedid="22" />
<notext extractedid="23" />
<notext extractedid="24" />
<notext extractedid="25" />
<notext extractedid="26" />
<notext extractedid="27" />
<notext extractedid="28" />
<notext extractedid="29" />
<notext extractedid="30" />
<notext extractedid="31" />
<notext extractedid="32" />
<notext extractedid="33" />
<notext extractedid="34" />
<notext extractedid="35" />
<notext extractedid="36" />
<notext extractedid="37" />
<notext extractedid="38" />
<notext extractedid="39" />
<notext extractedid="40" />
<notext extractedid="41" />
<notext extractedid="42" />
<notext extractedid="43" />
<notext extractedid="44" />
<notext extractedid="45" />
<notext extractedid="46" />
<notext extractedid="47" />
<notext extractedid="48" />
<notext extractedid="49" />
</file>
