<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes" ?>
<file name="TXT\en\MISS_002.ENG" compressed="true">
<text extractedid="0">
Third Day of the Second Year.


We have reached a second island which appears to be uninhabited. The stock of tools belonging to the good old Tortius is slowly being used up. We desperately need a metalworks to make new tools.
















</text>
<text extractedid="1">
Build a metalworks and move into the interior of the island. Pay close attention to the supply of provisions and raw materials.
</text>
<text extractedid="2">
We advanced a short distance northward and came across a fellow countryman. He was the only survivor of another shipwreck and he is very happy to see other humans again. We were also pleased; the man is a brewer. If we ever get into warlike disputes, beer will lift the courage of our people. A soldier needs much more than just a shield and a sword! 

The man also tells us of ruins that he has discovered on the island. I fear that before long we will need to be more careful.
















</text>
<text extractedid="3">
Advance into the interior of the island. Pay close attention to the supply of provisions and raw materials.
</text>
<text extractedid="4">
We have found the ruins. They contained building plans for a watchtower. Now we should consider building fortifications. I am more convinced than ever that we are not alone on this island.
















</text>
<text extractedid="5">
Advance into the interior of the island. Pay close attention to the supply of provisions and raw materials.
</text>
<text extractedid="6">
 We have found the ruins. They contained building plans for a watchtower. What is the origin of these structures? Who built them? I fear that peace will soon be at an end.
















</text>
<text extractedid="7">
Advance into the interior of the island. Pay close attention to the supply of provisions and raw materials.
</text>
<text extractedid="8">
Whoever is or was on this island knows all about the building trade. We found the ruins of a mighty fortress of exemplary construction. Our architects have already drawn up a building plan.
















</text>
<text extractedid="9">
Advance into the interior of the island. Pay close attention to the supply of provisions and raw materials.
</text>
<text extractedid="10">
26th Day of the Third Month of the Second Year.


My fears have been given further confirmation. My men found a rag doll and two spear tips of the type customarily associated with the Nubian tribes. These artifacts do not appear to be very old.
</text>
<text extractedid="11">

</text>
<text extractedid="12">
Our territory is expanding and transportation routes are becoming longer and longer. We must build a storehouse so that we can respond more quickly to the needs of our people.
</text>
<text extractedid="13">

</text>
<text extractedid="14">
Diary of Octavius.

Fourth Day of the Fourth Month of the Second Year.

It was only to be expected: we came across the Nubians. At first everything was very friendly. They even told us about their holy relic and it quickly became obvious that it was one of the gateways. They denied us access to their holy relic, we shall have to fight to obtain access.
















</text>
<text extractedid="15">
Attack the Nubians and gain access to their gateway.
</text>
<text extractedid="16">
The Nubians are lousy fighters but they have a catapult, which we must destroy. Perhaps then we shall be able to capture plans showing how to build such a weapon.
















</text>
<text extractedid="17">
Capture the catapult and then gain access to the gateway.
</text>
<text extractedid="18">
27th Day of the Ninth Month.


We were victorious in battle and the island is ours. The gateway has become active again. I am excited by the prospect of where our journey will take us now. The inscription on the gateway is in Latin. I hope that we will retrace the steps of our legendary predecessors when they journeyed to Rome...
















</text>
<text extractedid="19">
You have completed this mission. The third Chapter awaits you...
</text>
<notext extractedid="20" />
<notext extractedid="21" />
<notext extractedid="22" />
<notext extractedid="23" />
<notext extractedid="24" />
<notext extractedid="25" />
<notext extractedid="26" />
<notext extractedid="27" />
<notext extractedid="28" />
<notext extractedid="29" />
<notext extractedid="30" />
<notext extractedid="31" />
<notext extractedid="32" />
<notext extractedid="33" />
<notext extractedid="34" />
<notext extractedid="35" />
<notext extractedid="36" />
<notext extractedid="37" />
<notext extractedid="38" />
<notext extractedid="39" />
<notext extractedid="40" />
<notext extractedid="41" />
<notext extractedid="42" />
<notext extractedid="43" />
<notext extractedid="44" />
<notext extractedid="45" />
<notext extractedid="46" />
<notext extractedid="47" />
<notext extractedid="48" />
<notext extractedid="49" />
<notext extractedid="50" />
<notext extractedid="51" />
<notext extractedid="52" />
<notext extractedid="53" />
<notext extractedid="54" />
<notext extractedid="55" />
<notext extractedid="56" />
<notext extractedid="57" />
<notext extractedid="58" />
<notext extractedid="59" />
<notext extractedid="60" />
<notext extractedid="61" />
<notext extractedid="62" />
<notext extractedid="63" />
<notext extractedid="64" />
<notext extractedid="65" />
<notext extractedid="66" />
<notext extractedid="67" />
<notext extractedid="68" />
<notext extractedid="69" />
<notext extractedid="70" />
<notext extractedid="71" />
<notext extractedid="72" />
<notext extractedid="73" />
<notext extractedid="74" />
<notext extractedid="75" />
<notext extractedid="76" />
<notext extractedid="77" />
<notext extractedid="78" />
<notext extractedid="79" />
<notext extractedid="80" />
<notext extractedid="81" />
<notext extractedid="82" />
<notext extractedid="83" />
<notext extractedid="84" />
<notext extractedid="85" />
<notext extractedid="86" />
<notext extractedid="87" />
<notext extractedid="88" />
<notext extractedid="89" />
<notext extractedid="90" />
<notext extractedid="91" />
<notext extractedid="92" />
<notext extractedid="93" />
<notext extractedid="94" />
<notext extractedid="95" />
<notext extractedid="96" />
<notext extractedid="97" />
<notext extractedid="98" />
<notext extractedid="99" />
<notext extractedid="100" />
<notext extractedid="101" />
<notext extractedid="102" />
<notext extractedid="103" />
<notext extractedid="104" />
<notext extractedid="105" />
<notext extractedid="106" />
<notext extractedid="107" />
<notext extractedid="108" />
<notext extractedid="109" />
<notext extractedid="110" />
<notext extractedid="111" />
<notext extractedid="112" />
<notext extractedid="113" />
<notext extractedid="114" />
<notext extractedid="115" />
<notext extractedid="116" />
<notext extractedid="117" />
<notext extractedid="118" />
<notext extractedid="119" />
</file>
