<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes" ?>
<file name="TXT\en\MISS_004.ENG" compressed="true">
<text extractedid="0">
The Ninth Day of the Ninth Month of the Fourth Year.

Yesterday we met a stranger of truly frightening appearance. He is huge in size, has light blue eyes and glowing golden hair. Long ago in a Roman harbor tavern I once heard stories of such people who live in the far north. How did he get here? He is suspicious and refuses to talk to us. We shall treat him as our guest for a few days (the poor fellow appears to be starving). Perhaps then he will change his attitude.















</text>
<text extractedid="1">
Explore the surrounding area.
</text>
<text extractedid="2">
16th Day of the Ninth Month of the Fourth Year.

Well, what wonders a little generosity can achieve. The blond giant told us that he is a member of a race that calls itself the "Vikings". He says that they lived on a large island not far to the east but they were conquered by a hostile tribe. His name is Erik. What a strange name! If we are to believe him, he is a shipwright by trade. My heart beats faster at the prospect of soon being able to board a ship again, hearing the waves under the keel, the cries of the seagulls and the wind in the sails...
But first of all we must construct a shipyard and a harbor.















</text>
<text extractedid="3">
Build a harbor and a shipyard. In the shipyard build a large trading ship and organize an expedition from the harbor.
</text>
<text extractedid="4">
On a small island in the middle of a archipelago, we discovered an enormous whale graveyard, in which there were hundreds of gigantic skeletons. What an imposing sight. At first we were unable to understand how these creatures got there. Erik explained that his people lived off these creatures and worshipped them as holy animals. This was why their bones were brought to this sacred place after they were caught. Erik is uneasy, he wants to leave because he is afraid of the spirits of the dead creatures.















</text>
<text extractedid="5">
Explore the island further. Search for the next gateway.
</text>
<text extractedid="6">
We have reached the gateway and activated it. The way is now clear.



















 
</text>
<text extractedid="7">
You have completed this mission. The next Chapter awaits you...
</text>
<notext extractedid="8" />
<notext extractedid="9" />
<notext extractedid="10" />
<notext extractedid="11" />
<notext extractedid="12" />
<notext extractedid="13" />
<notext extractedid="14" />
<notext extractedid="15" />
<notext extractedid="16" />
<notext extractedid="17" />
<notext extractedid="18" />
<notext extractedid="19" />
<notext extractedid="20" />
<notext extractedid="21" />
<notext extractedid="22" />
<notext extractedid="23" />
<notext extractedid="24" />
<notext extractedid="25" />
<notext extractedid="26" />
<notext extractedid="27" />
<notext extractedid="28" />
<notext extractedid="29" />
<notext extractedid="30" />
<notext extractedid="31" />
<notext extractedid="32" />
<notext extractedid="33" />
<notext extractedid="34" />
<notext extractedid="35" />
<notext extractedid="36" />
<notext extractedid="37" />
<notext extractedid="38" />
<notext extractedid="39" />
<notext extractedid="40" />
<notext extractedid="41" />
<notext extractedid="42" />
<notext extractedid="43" />
<notext extractedid="44" />
<notext extractedid="45" />
<notext extractedid="46" />
<notext extractedid="47" />
<notext extractedid="48" />
<notext extractedid="49" />
</file>
