<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes" ?>
<file name="TXT\en\MISS_001.ENG" compressed="true">
<text extractedid="0">
Diary of Octavius:


Fourth Day After Shipwreck.


Yesterday all the survivors met in order to discuss the situation. Because there is no prospect of an early rescue, we decided to settle on this foreign island. The items salvaged from the ship will be a great help to us. The most important thing is to make use of the raw materials on the island in order to establish a settlement. We urgently need accommodations for a woodcutter, carpenter and stonemason.
</text>
<text extractedid="1">
Build accommodations for a woodcutter, carpenter and stonemason.
</text>
<text extractedid="2">
Eighth Day After Shipwreck.


The basic requirements for building up our settlement have been met. However, the supply of trees in this region will not last long. We need a forester to ensure a long-term supply of timber.
</text>
<text extractedid="3">
Build a forester.
</text>
<text extractedid="4">
Eleventh Day of the Second Month After Shipwreck.


We are still not sure whether we are the only people on this island. As a precautionary measure we should erect a barracks on our exposed border towards the interior of the island.
</text>
<text extractedid="5">
Build a barracks on the northern border of your settlement.
</text>
<text extractedid="6">
Fifth Day of the Third Month.


Our territory has spread as far as the mountain in the north. Our geologist will carry out a land survey there. In the long term we need fuel and building materials as well as weapons and coined gold. We must therefore find a source of iron ore, gold, coal and granite.
</text>
<text extractedid="7">
Build a road to the mountain and send your geologist there.
</text>
<text extractedid="8">
Sixteenth Day of the Sixth Month.


We have found iron ore and are now able to produce weapons. There are now no obstacles to further exploration of the island. First we must construct both an iron mine and an iron smelter. An armorer can then start to produce swords and shields. We must also provide the miners with food, our stocks are almost exhausted. We need hunters and fishermen!
</text>
<text extractedid="9">
Build an iron mine, an iron smelter and an armory.
</text>
<text extractedid="10">
Last Day of the Eighth Month After Coming Ashore.


There is an open, fertile plain to the north of our new border post. This will provide lots of new opportunities for expanding our settlement but we need more soldiers to do this.
</text>
<text extractedid="11">
Go to the northern plain and continue expanding the border.
</text>
<text extractedid="12">
Twelfth Day of the Ninth Month.


After advancing further north we have finally found enough space to construct larger buildings and farms. We now intend to search for raw materials in the surrounding mountains.
</text>
<text extractedid="13">
Search for new raw materials and secure a supply of food. Explore the entire island.
</text>
<text extractedid="14">
We have discovered a gold vein and can now produce valuable coins in a mint. This will make life here almost as comfortable as at home.
</text>
<text extractedid="15">

</text>
<text extractedid="16">
We have ensured a fuel supply for the metalworks by finding coal in the western mountains. Now we can process our metal ores without any problems. Everything is going extremely well.
</text>
<text extractedid="17">

</text>
<text extractedid="18">
Geologists have found granite deposits in the mountains, this will provide a fresh supply of stone for the time being.
</text>
<text extractedid="19">

</text>
<text extractedid="20">
Our geologist has found a spring. We are now able to supply fresh water to our settlement.
</text>
<text extractedid="21">

</text>
<text extractedid="22">
We have minted the first gold coins and can now pay for the training of our soldiers.
</text>
<text extractedid="23">

</text>
<text extractedid="24">
Construction of our first grain farm has been completed. The grain can either be processed into flour in a mill, or used to feed pigs. The food supply situation should now continue to improve.
</text>
<text extractedid="25">

</text>
<text extractedid="26">
Our new pig farm can supply animals to a butcher.
</text>
<text extractedid="27">

</text>
<text extractedid="28">
The windmill can supply a baker with sufficient flour for baking bread.
</text>
<text extractedid="29">

</text>
<text extractedid="30">
Our scouts have discovered a strange object. It looks like a gateway. We are obviously not the first humans on this island. They have even found an inscription on the gateway in Latin. It is bizarre and contradictory, perhaps it is a riddle: "Consiste ut procederas!" - "Settle down in order to make progress!". What can this mean?
</text>
<text extractedid="31">

</text>
<notext extractedid="32" />
<notext extractedid="33" />
<notext extractedid="34" />
<notext extractedid="35" />
<notext extractedid="36" />
<notext extractedid="37" />
<notext extractedid="38" />
<notext extractedid="39" />
<notext extractedid="40" />
<notext extractedid="41" />
<notext extractedid="42" />
<notext extractedid="43" />
<notext extractedid="44" />
<notext extractedid="45" />
<notext extractedid="46" />
<notext extractedid="47" />
<notext extractedid="48" />
<notext extractedid="49" />
<notext extractedid="50" />
<notext extractedid="51" />
<notext extractedid="52" />
<notext extractedid="53" />
<notext extractedid="54" />
<notext extractedid="55" />
<notext extractedid="56" />
<notext extractedid="57" />
<notext extractedid="58" />
<notext extractedid="59" />
<notext extractedid="60" />
<notext extractedid="61" />
<notext extractedid="62" />
<notext extractedid="63" />
<notext extractedid="64" />
<notext extractedid="65" />
<notext extractedid="66" />
<notext extractedid="67" />
<notext extractedid="68" />
<notext extractedid="69" />
<notext extractedid="70" />
<notext extractedid="71" />
<notext extractedid="72" />
<notext extractedid="73" />
<notext extractedid="74" />
<notext extractedid="75" />
<notext extractedid="76" />
<notext extractedid="77" />
<notext extractedid="78" />
<notext extractedid="79" />
<notext extractedid="80" />
<notext extractedid="81" />
<notext extractedid="82" />
<notext extractedid="83" />
<notext extractedid="84" />
<notext extractedid="85" />
<notext extractedid="86" />
<notext extractedid="87" />
<notext extractedid="88" />
<notext extractedid="89" />
<notext extractedid="90" />
<notext extractedid="91" />
<notext extractedid="92" />
<notext extractedid="93" />
<notext extractedid="94" />
<notext extractedid="95" />
<notext extractedid="96" />
<notext extractedid="97" />
<notext extractedid="98" />
<notext extractedid="99" />
<text extractedid="100">
Second Day of the Thirteenth Month After Coming Ashore.


The second year began yesterday and we seem to have succeeded in settling this island. The scouts report strange goings on near the gateway. It appears that a path has opened up that can lead us from this island. This seems to be the meaning of the riddle: we must settle in order to move on. We shall take a look, perhaps all roads really do lead to Rome.









</text>
<text extractedid="101">
You have completed this mission. The second Chapter awaits you... 

 You can begin the next mission from the main menu whenever you want.
</text>
<notext extractedid="102" />
<notext extractedid="103" />
<notext extractedid="104" />
<notext extractedid="105" />
<notext extractedid="106" />
<notext extractedid="107" />
<notext extractedid="108" />
<notext extractedid="109" />
<notext extractedid="110" />
<notext extractedid="111" />
<notext extractedid="112" />
<notext extractedid="113" />
<notext extractedid="114" />
<notext extractedid="115" />
<notext extractedid="116" />
<notext extractedid="117" />
<notext extractedid="118" />
<notext extractedid="119" />
</file>
