<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" standalone="yes" ?>
<file name="TXT\en\MISS_010.ENG" compressed="true">
<text extractedid="0">
The 17th Day of the Sixth Month of the 10th Year.

Romans are actually standing in front of the tenth gateway. They are not at all friendly. Perhaps they are the other side of the coin, the enemy brother Remus. Maybe their gateway is the one that will take us back to our beloved Rome.
As the old legend says:
"For the sake of Rome brother shall fight against brother." For almost ten years we have been constantly dreaming of our homeland. We shall not give up now.









</text>
<text extractedid="1">
Muster all of your forces in order to break through! Capture the gateway!
</text>
<text extractedid="2">
Last Day of the 10th Year.
Last entry of Octavius in this Diary

 We have succeeded. Tomorrow we shall return to Rome exactly ten years after becoming castaways on this island. Ten years during which we traveled in the footsteps of our forefathers. Ten years during which we learned what made Rome so great. We shall offer a great feast of thanks to the gods and will see our families and friends again.
I can hardly wait.










</text>
<text extractedid="3">
You have succeeded!
</text>
<text extractedid="4">
The air is filled with anticipation and even a little reluctance, as we prepare to embark on the final and most dangerous chapter of our long journey home. Will we ever see Rome again?  We must summon all our strength because this island seems to be our best chance...


















</text>
<text extractedid="5">
Be careful. Do not attack until you are sure you can defeat both enemies.
</text>
<notext extractedid="6" />
<notext extractedid="7" />
<notext extractedid="8" />
<notext extractedid="9" />
<notext extractedid="10" />
<notext extractedid="11" />
<notext extractedid="12" />
<notext extractedid="13" />
<notext extractedid="14" />
<notext extractedid="15" />
<notext extractedid="16" />
<notext extractedid="17" />
<notext extractedid="18" />
<notext extractedid="19" />
<notext extractedid="20" />
<notext extractedid="21" />
<notext extractedid="22" />
<notext extractedid="23" />
<notext extractedid="24" />
<notext extractedid="25" />
<notext extractedid="26" />
<notext extractedid="27" />
<notext extractedid="28" />
<notext extractedid="29" />
<notext extractedid="30" />
<notext extractedid="31" />
<notext extractedid="32" />
<notext extractedid="33" />
<notext extractedid="34" />
<notext extractedid="35" />
<notext extractedid="36" />
<notext extractedid="37" />
<notext extractedid="38" />
<notext extractedid="39" />
<notext extractedid="40" />
<notext extractedid="41" />
<notext extractedid="42" />
<notext extractedid="43" />
<notext extractedid="44" />
<notext extractedid="45" />
<notext extractedid="46" />
<notext extractedid="47" />
<notext extractedid="48" />
<notext extractedid="49" />
</file>
